honeyflow.com 2018-11-28

# BeeInventive's Privacy Policy - Flow Hive

_Last updated: 24 May 2018_

BeeInventive Pty Ltd  ACN: 161 952 941 (operator and licensee of the Flow brand, subsequently referred to as “we”) is subject to current Australian privacy legislation. We believe that the compliance with the Australian privacy legislation also makes us compliant with US data and privacy protection rules. You can read our Privacy Policy and Cookies Notice for our European Economic Area customers on our EU [website](https://eu.honeyflow.com/). 

We fully respect the confidentiality of your information and take your privacy very seriously. In line with applicable legislation we explain in this privacy policy

  * why we need your personal information and what types of information we collect from you;
  * how we make sure your personal information remains safe and secure;
  * how you can contact us to find out more about your personal information.

## Why we need your personal information?

In this Privacy Policy, personal information is any information that could identify or be used to establish your identity. We collect your personal information so that we may fulfil your orders, advise you of the latest developments in our business and create a vibrant bee keeping community.

We engage in design, development, manufacturing, distribution and marketing of Flow Hives and other bee keeping equipment. We mainly collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information so that we can design, manufacture and deliver our products to you.

We may use your personal information to keep you informed about the latest offers related to our products, bee keeping related activities and bee keeping educational resources. You can opt out of receiving direct marketing information from us at any time.

## What types of personal information do we collect?

We may ask for a range of personal information to assist us in delivering our products to you and collecting payments from you. The information we may request includes (but is not limited to) name, address, date of birth, contact details, email address, credit and debit card details. We gather all your personal information through the internet forms and subscribe buttons.

If you wish to remain anonymous or to use a pseudonym when dealing with us, we may be able to provide you with limited information, such as general details about our products. However, in many cases it will be impracticable for us to assist you if you wish to remain anonymous or use a pseudonym. For example, we will not be able to deliver our products to you if you do not provide us with your personal details. 

## How do we protect your personal information?

We hold your personal information in a computer storage facility and take steps to store them securely. We take a number of steps to protect personal information from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or improper disclosure. These include instructing our staff who handle personal information to respect the confidentiality of customer information and the privacy of individuals.

From time to time we may share your personal information with other entities, some of them may be located, or have operations in, other countries. Such countries include the United States of America, Canada, the Netherlands and Hong Kong. We require any external organisation with whom we share your personal information to comply with the Australian Privacy Principles.

We aim to hold the personal information correct and up to date. If we believe the information we hold is incomplete or out of date, we may seek to correct or complete our records from other sources. Alternatively, you can alter the information we hold by contacting customer service department.

We may be legally required to maintain some of your records for a significant period of time. However, once we believe information is not longer needed we may remove any identifying details or destroy the records entirely. 

## How can you contact us about privacy?

You can contact us to:

  * seek more information about anything contained in this policy, or to request a copy of this policy in a different format;
  * update or correct your personal information;
  * opt out of receiving direct marketing material;
  * ask about accessing or correcting the personal information we hold about you; or
  * make a privacy related complaint;

in one of the following ways:

  * By telephone: +61 2 8880 0774
  * By email: [info@honeyflow.com](mailto:info@honeyflow.com)
  * In writing: P.O. Box 303, Bangalow, NSW 2478, Australia.

Under the Privacy Act you have the right to access the personal information we hold about you, with some exceptions. To make a request you need to contact us through the channels as set out above.

We are permitted to refuse you access to the personal information in certain situations. Examples include where:

  * giving access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of other individuals;
  * giving access would be unlawful, or where denying access is required or authorised by an Australian law or a court order;
  * both of the following apply:

(i) we have reason to suspect that unlawful activity, or misconduct of a serious nature, that relates to our functions or activities has been, is being or may be engaged in; and

(ii) giving access would be likely to prejudice the taking of appropriate action in relation to the matter;

  * giving access is likely to interfere with law enforcement activities.

Before providing the requested information we will give you an estimate of any potential costs associated with this, including expenses for locating, retrieving, reviewing and copying any of the material you need.

## What should you do if you have a concern?

To raise any concerns you might have in relation to privacy, please contact us via the contact channels listed above. We take privacy-related complaints very seriously and consider all complaints carefully as part of our commitment to being open, honest and fair in dealing with your concerns.

If, despite our best efforts, you still have concerns further assistance may be available from:

The Office of the Australian Information Commissioner  
Phone: 1300 363 992  
Website: [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/)  
Email: [enquiries@oaic.gov.au](mailto:enquiries@oaic.gov.au)

## Privacy and the Internet

This section outlines some privacy issues specific to honeyflow.com.au, honeyflow.com and eu.honeyflow.com websites.

Cookies are small pieces of text stored on your computer to help us determine the type of browser and settings you are using, where you have been on the web site, when you return to the web site, where you came from, and to ensure your information is secure. The purpose of this information is to provide you with a more relevant and effective experience on our websites.

We use cookies to give you access to certain pages of the websites without having to log in each time you visit. We may also use external service providers to track the traffic and usage on the web site.

Cookies are frequently used on many websites on the internet and you can choose if and how a cookie will be accepted by changing your preferences and options in your browser. You may not be able to access some parts of honeyflow.com.au or honeyflow.com if you choose to disable the cookie acceptance in your browser, particularly the shopping cart and the secure parts of the websites such as My account area. We therefore recommend you enable cookie acceptance to benefit from all the services on the website.

Website analytics measurement software is used to assist in tracking traffic patterns to and from our websites, surveying users of the sites. The system is used to collect such information as the number of unique visitors, how long these visitors spend on the website when they do visit, and common entry and exit points into and from the websites. This information is collected and aggregated by third party software and provided to us to assist in our analysis of the websites.

## About this Policy

Any information we hold is governed by our most current Privacy Policy. The policy is publicly available via our websites honeyflow.com.au and honeyflow.com, or you can contact us about obtaining the policy in different formats. This policy is reviewed from time to time to take account of new laws and technology, and changes to our operations and practices, and to make sure it remains appropriate to the changing environment.
